SHELDON:
Leonard...
(Sheldon:)I've got terrible news.
(Leonard:)What's going on?
(Sheldon:)Before I tell you,
(Sheldon:)perhaps I should
soften the blow.
Your face
is pleasingly symmetrical.
(Leonard:)Just tell me.
(Sheldon:)A Swedish team of physicists
(Sheldon:)is trying to scoop our super-
fluid vortex experiment.
(Leonard:)Oh, well, that kind of stinks.
“That kind of stinks”?
(Sheldon:)Why aren't you more upset?
(Sheldon:)Did I soften the blow too much?
(Sheldon:)Because this here is more
like a Picasso painting.
(Leonard:)What are we going to do?
(Sheldon:)Perform the experiment
immediately.
(Leonard:)I'd love to,
but we need liquid helium
(Leonard:)and our shipment's
on back order for a month.
(Sheldon:)A month? What?
Are you kidding me?
(Sheldon:)That would have been a good time
for you to soften the blow.
(Leonard:)That shirt brings out
the blue in your eyes.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
Aren't you sweet.
(Leonard:)Let's go check to see
if the university
(Leonard:)has any helium in reserve.
(Sheldon:)Did you know that I almost
didn't wear this shirt today?